<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>discovery&#43; on </title>
    <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/network/discovery&#43;/</link>
    <description>Recent content in discovery&#43; on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 11:01:24 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bestepisodes.xyz/network/discovery+/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Mythbusters Best Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/mythbusters-best-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 11:01:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/mythbusters-best-episodes/</guid>
      <description>MythBusters is a science entertainment television program created and produced by Australia&amp;rsquo;s Beyond Television Productions for the Discovery Channel. The show&amp;rsquo;s hosts, special effects experts Adam Savage and Jamie Hyneman, use elements of the scientific method to test the validity of rumors, myths, movie scenes, adages, Internet videos, and news stories. Mythbusters is an American documentary series that was first aired in 2003. See the best episodes of Mythbusters below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best River Monster Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-river-monsters-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 13:12:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-river-monsters-episodes/</guid>
      <description>Extreme angler Jeremy Wade is on the hunt for fish with a taste for human flesh. This rip-roaring ride mixes action and adventure with mysteries, edge-of-the-seat chase and a battle of wills between man and nature. The series was first premiered in 2009 that follows the biologist Jeremy Wade on his adventures with the river monsters around the world. See best episodes of River Monsters below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Ghost Adventures Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-ghost-adventures-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-ghost-adventures-episodes/</guid>
      <description>Paranormal investigator Zak Bagans and his crew, Nick Groff and Aaron Goodwin, search for haunted locations both domestically and internationally. During their investigations, Zak and crew acquaint themselves with the general area; interview locals about the hauntings; and go face-to-face with the evil spirits who reportedly haunt these locations.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
