<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>the-cw on </title>
    <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/network/the-cw/</link>
    <description>Recent content in the-cw on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 22:38:26 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bestepisodes.xyz/network/the-cw/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Best The 100 Episodes List</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-the-100-episodes-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 22:38:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-the-100-episodes-list/</guid>
      <description>100 years in the future, when the Earth has been abandoned due to radioactivity, the last surviving humans live on an ark orbiting the planet — but the ark won&amp;rsquo;t last forever. So the repressive regime picks 100 expendable juvenile delinquents to send down to Earth to see if the planet is still habitable. The 100 is an American fantasy mystery tv-series that was first aired in 2004. See the best episodes of The 100 below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Riverdale Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-riverdale-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 20:01:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-riverdale-episodes/</guid>
      <description>Set in the present, the series offers a bold, subversive take on Archie, Betty, Veronica and their friends, exploring the surreality of small-town life, the darkness and weirdness bubbling beneath Riverdale’s wholesome facade. Riverdale is an American crime drama tv-series that was first aired in 2017. See the best episodes of Riverdale below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Arrow Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-arrow-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 11:46:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-arrow-episodes/</guid>
      <description>Spoiled billionaire playboy Oliver Queen is missing and presumed dead when his yacht is lost at sea. He returns five years later a changed man, determined to clean up the city as a hooded vigilante armed with a bow. Arrow is an American fantasy mystery tv-series that was first aired in 2012 on The CW. See the best episodes of Arrow below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Episodes of the Vampire Diaries</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-the-vampire-diaries/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 07:18:18 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-the-vampire-diaries/</guid>
      <description>The story of two vampire brothers obsessed with the same girl, who bears a striking resemblance to the beautiful but ruthless vampire they knew and loved in 1864. The Vampire Diaries is an American teen romance supernatural tv-series that was first aired in 2009. See The Vampire Diaries best episodes below.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
