<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>horror on </title>
    <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/genres/horror/</link>
    <description>Recent content in horror on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 21:13:36 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bestepisodes.xyz/genres/horror/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Best Tales From the Darkside Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-tales-from-the-darkside-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 21:13:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-tales-from-the-darkside-episodes/</guid>
      <description>Tales from the Darkside is an anthology horror TV series created by George A. Romero; it was released in 1984. Similar to Amazing Stories, The Twilight Zone, Night Gallery, The Outer Limits, Tales From The Crypt, and Lee Martin&amp;rsquo;s The Midnight Hour, each episode was an individual short story that ended with a plot twist. The series&#39; episodes spanned the genres of horror, science fiction, and fantasy, and some episodes featured elements of black comedy or more lighthearted themes. Tales from the Darkside is an American thriller science-fiction tv-series that first aired in 1984 and ran till 1988. See the best episodes of Tales from the Darkside below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best R.L. Stine&#39;s The Haunting Hour Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-the-haunting-hour-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 18:57:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-the-haunting-hour-episodes/</guid>
      <description>R. L. Stine&amp;rsquo;s The Haunting Hour is a Canadian/American original anthology horror-fantasy series, with episodes each half an hour long. The series is based on The Haunting Hour: Don&amp;rsquo;t Think About It Movie, and the books The Haunting Hour and Nightmare Hour anthology by R. L. Stine. R.L. Stine&amp;rsquo;s The haunting hour is an American-Canadian horror fantasy tv-series that was first aired in 2010. See the best episodes of The Haunting Hour below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Alfred Hitchcock Hour Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-alfred-hitchcock-hour-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 10:24:15 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-alfred-hitchcock-hour-episodes/</guid>
      <description>A continuation of the dramatic anthology series &amp;lsquo;Alfred Hitchcock Presents&amp;rsquo;, hosted by the master of suspense and mystery. Alfred Hitchcock Hour is an American horror thriller tv-series that was first aired in 1962. See the best episodes of Alfred Hitchcock Hour below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Episodes of the Walking Dead</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-the-walking-dead/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 14:26:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-the-walking-dead/</guid>
      <description>Sheriff&amp;rsquo;s deputy Rick Grimes awakens from a coma to find a post-apocalyptic world dominated by flesh-eating zombies. He sets out to find his family and encounters many other survivors along the way. The Walking Dead is an American horror, action &amp;amp; adventure tv-series that was first aired in 2010. See The Walking Dead best episodes below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Room 104 Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-room-104-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 11:30:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-room-104-episodes/</guid>
      <description>An anthology series set in a single hotel room, where every guest who comes to stay reveals a unique set of circumstances and quirks. Room 104 is an American horror thriller tv-series that was first aired in 2017 on HBO. See the best episodes of Room 104 below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Outer Limits Best Episodes (1995)</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/outer-limits-best-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 07:34:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/outer-limits-best-episodes/</guid>
      <description>The Outer Limits is an anthology series of distinct story episodes, sometimes with a plot twist at the end. Unlike the original incarnation of the series, which was a pure anthology with each episode completely unrelated to the others, the revival series maintained an anthology format, but occasionally featured recurring story elements that were often tied together during season-finale clip shows. The Outer Limits is an American science horror anthology tv-series that was first aired in 1995. See the best episodes of The Outer Limits below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Episodes of the Vampire Diaries</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-the-vampire-diaries/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 07:18:18 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-the-vampire-diaries/</guid>
      <description>The story of two vampire brothers obsessed with the same girl, who bears a striking resemblance to the beautiful but ruthless vampire they knew and loved in 1864. The Vampire Diaries is an American teen romance supernatural tv-series that was first aired in 2009. See The Vampire Diaries best episodes below.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
