<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>fantasy on </title>
    <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/genres/fantasy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in fantasy on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 16:40:47 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bestepisodes.xyz/genres/fantasy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Best Fairy Tail Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-fairy-tail-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 16:40:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-fairy-tail-episodes/</guid>
      <description>Lucy is a 17-year-old girl, who wants to be a full-fledged mage. One day when visiting Harujion Town, she meets Natsu, a young man who gets sick easily by any type of transportation. But Natsu isn&amp;rsquo;t just any ordinary kid, he&amp;rsquo;s a member of one of the world&amp;rsquo;s most infamous mage guilds: Fairy Tail. Fairy Tail is a Japanese adventure and fantasy anime that was first aired in 2009 on Tv Tokyo network. See the best episodes of Fairy Tail below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best One Piece Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-one-piece-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 15:24:38 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-one-piece-episodes/</guid>
      <description>Years ago, the fearsome pirate king Gol D. Roger was executed, leaving a huge pile of treasure and the famous &amp;lsquo;One Piece&amp;rsquo; behind. Whoever claims the &amp;lsquo;One Piece&amp;rsquo; will be named the new pirate king. Monkey D. Luffy, a boy who consumed one of the &amp;lsquo;Devil&amp;rsquo;s Fruits&amp;rsquo;, has it in his head that he&amp;rsquo;ll follow in the footsteps of his idol, the pirate Shanks, and find the One Piece. It helps, of course, that his body has the properties of rubber and he&amp;rsquo;s surrounded by a bevy of skilled fighters and thieves to help him along the way. Monkey D. Luffy brings a bunch of his crew followed by, Roronoa Zoro, Nami, Usopp, Sanji, Tony-Tony Chopper, Nico Robin, Franky, and Brook. They will do anything to get the One Piece and become King of the Pirates! One Piece is a Japanese action and adventure anime that was first aired in 1999. See the best episodes of One Piece below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Arrow Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-arrow-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 11:46:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-arrow-episodes/</guid>
      <description>Spoiled billionaire playboy Oliver Queen is missing and presumed dead when his yacht is lost at sea. He returns five years later a changed man, determined to clean up the city as a hooded vigilante armed with a bow. Arrow is an American fantasy mystery tv-series that was first aired in 2012 on The CW. See the best episodes of Arrow below.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
