<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>fantasy on </title>
    <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/genres/fantasy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in fantasy on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 00:12:37 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bestepisodes.xyz/genres/fantasy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Best Episodes of the Boys</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-the-boys/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 00:12:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-the-boys/</guid>
      <description>A group of vigilantes known informally as “The Boys” set out to take down corrupt superheroes with no more than blue-collar grit and a willingness to fight dirty. The Boys is an American action fantasy thriller tv-series that was first aired in 2019. See best episodes of The Boys below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Tales From the Darkside Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-tales-from-the-darkside-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 21:13:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-tales-from-the-darkside-episodes/</guid>
      <description>Tales from the Darkside is an anthology horror TV series created by George A. Romero; it was released in 1984. Similar to Amazing Stories, The Twilight Zone, Night Gallery, The Outer Limits, Tales From The Crypt, and Lee Martin&amp;rsquo;s The Midnight Hour, each episode was an individual short story that ended with a plot twist. The series&#39; episodes spanned the genres of horror, science fiction, and fantasy, and some episodes featured elements of black comedy or more lighthearted themes. Tales from the Darkside is an American thriller science-fiction tv-series that first aired in 1984 and ran till 1988. See the best episodes of Tales from the Darkside below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Bleach Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-bleach-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 09:15:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-bleach-episodes/</guid>
      <description>For as long as he can remember, Ichigo Kurosaki has been able to see ghosts. But when he meets Rukia, a Soul Reaper who battles evil spirits known as Hollows, he finds his life is changed forever. Now, with a newfound wealth of spiritual energy, Ichigo discovers his true calling: to protect the living and the dead from evil. Bleach is a Japanese action fantasy anime that was first aired in 2004. See the best episodes of Bleach below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best the 100 Episodes List</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-the-100-episodes-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 22:38:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-the-100-episodes-list/</guid>
      <description>100 years in the future, when the Earth has been abandoned due to radioactivity, the last surviving humans live on an ark orbiting the planet — but the ark won&amp;rsquo;t last forever. So the repressive regime picks 100 expendable juvenile delinquents to send down to Earth to see if the planet is still habitable. The 100 is an American fantasy mystery tv-series that was first aired in 2004. See the best episodes of The 100 below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Sweet Punishment: I&#39;m the Guard&#39;s Personal Pet Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-sweet-punishment-im-the-guards-personal-pet-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 22:20:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-sweet-punishment-im-the-guards-personal-pet-episodes/</guid>
      <description>The story is set in a prison in the near future. It revolves around Hina Saotome, imprisoned despite her innocence, and the elegant yet sadistic guard Aki Myoujin. Hina&amp;rsquo;s heart and body are at the mercy of Myoujin&amp;rsquo;s heartless yet sweet domination from physical examinations to lovers&#39; prison visits. Sweet Punishment is a Japanese romance fantasy anime that was first aired on Tokyo MX. See the best episodes of Sweet Punishment below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Fairy Tail Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-fairy-tail-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 16:40:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-fairy-tail-episodes/</guid>
      <description>Lucy is a 17-year-old girl, who wants to be a full-fledged mage. One day when visiting Harujion Town, she meets Natsu, a young man who gets sick easily by any type of transportation. But Natsu isn&amp;rsquo;t just any ordinary kid, he&amp;rsquo;s a member of one of the world&amp;rsquo;s most infamous mage guilds: Fairy Tail. Fairy Tail is a Japanese adventure and fantasy anime that was first aired in 2009 on Tv Tokyo network. See the best episodes of Fairy Tail below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best One Piece Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-one-piece-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 15:24:38 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-one-piece-episodes/</guid>
      <description>Years ago, the fearsome pirate king Gol D. Roger was executed, leaving a huge pile of treasure and the famous &amp;lsquo;One Piece&amp;rsquo; behind. Whoever claims the &amp;lsquo;One Piece&amp;rsquo; will be named the new pirate king. Monkey D. Luffy, a boy who consumed one of the &amp;lsquo;Devil&amp;rsquo;s Fruits&amp;rsquo;, has it in his head that he&amp;rsquo;ll follow in the footsteps of his idol, the pirate Shanks, and find the One Piece. It helps, of course, that his body has the properties of rubber and he&amp;rsquo;s surrounded by a bevy of skilled fighters and thieves to help him along the way. Monkey D. Luffy brings a bunch of his crew followed by, Roronoa Zoro, Nami, Usopp, Sanji, Tony-Tony Chopper, Nico Robin, Franky, and Brook. They will do anything to get the One Piece and become King of the Pirates! One Piece is a Japanese action and adventure anime that was first aired in 1999. See the best episodes of One Piece below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Arrow Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-arrow-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 11:46:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-arrow-episodes/</guid>
      <description>Spoiled billionaire playboy Oliver Queen is missing and presumed dead when his yacht is lost at sea. He returns five years later a changed man, determined to clean up the city as a hooded vigilante armed with a bow. Arrow is an American fantasy mystery tv-series that was first aired in 2012 on The CW. See the best episodes of Arrow below.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
