<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>romance on </title>
    <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/genres/romance/</link>
    <description>Recent content in romance on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 14:13:02 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bestepisodes.xyz/genres/romance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Best Episodes of The Big Bang Theory</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-big-bang-theory/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 14:13:02 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-big-bang-theory/</guid>
      <description>The sitcom is centered on five characters living in Pasadena, California: roommates Leonard Hofstadter and Sheldon Cooper; Penny, a waitress and aspiring actress who lives across the hall; and Leonard and Sheldon&amp;rsquo;s equally geeky and socially awkward friends and co-workers, mechanical engineer Howard Wolowitz and astrophysicist Raj Koothrappali. The geekiness and intellect of the four guys is contrasted for comic effect with Penny&amp;rsquo;s social skills and common sense. The Big Bang Theory is an American sitcom tv-series that was first aired in 2007 on CBS. See the best The Big Bang Theory episodes below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Episodes of One Tree Hill</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-one-tree-hill/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 10:47:15 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-one-tree-hill/</guid>
      <description>Set in the fictional small town of Tree Hill, North Carolina, this teen-driven drama tells the story of two half brothers, who share a last name and nothing else. Brooding, blue-collar Lucas is a talented street-side basketball player, but his skills are appreciated only by his friends at the river court. Popular, affluent Nathan basks in the hero-worship of the town, as the star of his high school team. And both boys are the son of former college ball player, Dan Scott, whose long ago choice to abandon Lucas and his mother Karen, will haunt him long into his life with wife Deb, and their son Nathan. One Tree Hill is an American romance drama tv-series that was first aired in 2003. See the best One Tree Hill episodes below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Episodes of the Vampire Diaries</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-the-vampire-diaries/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 07:18:18 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-the-vampire-diaries/</guid>
      <description>The story of two vampire brothers obsessed with the same girl, who bears a striking resemblance to the beautiful but ruthless vampire they knew and loved in 1864. The Vampire Diaries is an American teen romance supernatural tv-series that was first aired in 2009. See The Vampire Diaries best episodes below.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
