<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>reality on </title>
    <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/genres/reality/</link>
    <description>Recent content in reality on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 11:10:52 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bestepisodes.xyz/genres/reality/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Best Doomsday Preppers Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-doomsday-preppers-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 11:10:52 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-doomsday-preppers-episodes/</guid>
      <description>Doomsday Preppers is an American reality television series that airs on the National Geographic Channel. Dräger Equipment, Wise Food Storage Company and the United States Gold Bureau are sponsors of the show. Doomsday Preppers is an American reality documentary tv-series that was first aired in 2011 on National Geographic. See the best episodes of Doomsday Preppers below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mythbusters Best Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/mythbusters-best-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 11:01:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/mythbusters-best-episodes/</guid>
      <description>MythBusters is a science entertainment television program created and produced by Australia&amp;rsquo;s Beyond Television Productions for the Discovery Channel. The show&amp;rsquo;s hosts, special effects experts Adam Savage and Jamie Hyneman, use elements of the scientific method to test the validity of rumors, myths, movie scenes, adages, Internet videos, and news stories. Mythbusters is an American documentary series that was first aired in 2003. See the best episodes of Mythbusters below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Forged in Fire Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-forged-in-fire-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 10:23:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-forged-in-fire-episodes/</guid>
      <description>Competitors re-create weapons from historical periods ranging from Japanese katanas to medieval broadswords to ancient throwing blades. Each entry is judged on its artistry as well as its functionality and accuracy. Forged in Fire is an American reality game-show tv-series that was first aired in 2015. See the best episodes of Forged in Fire below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Episodes of Jersey Shore</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-jersey-shore/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 08:48:45 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-jersey-shore/</guid>
      <description>Grab your hair gel, wax that Cadillac and get those tattooed biceps ready to fist pump with the best this summer at the Jersey Shore. MTV&amp;rsquo;s newest docu-soap exposes one of the tri-state area&amp;rsquo;s most misunderstood species, the Guido. Our Guidos and Guidettes will move into the ultimate beach house rental and indulge in everything the Seaside Heights, New Jersey scene has to offer. Beach by day, dancing and partying all night. They&amp;rsquo;ll live, work, and rage together until the summer ends. There&amp;rsquo;s no spray tan too orange, no hair too spiked, and no bod too tight for this crew. Jersey Shore is an American reality drama tv-series that was first aired in 2009. See the best Jersey Shore episodes below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Bar Rescue Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-bar-rescue-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 06:54:14 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-bar-rescue-episodes/</guid>
      <description>Jon Taffer is the Gordon Ramsay of the bar and nightclub business. In each episode, Taffer helps transform a struggling bar into a vibrant, profitable business, utilizing his expertise as a nightlife consultant. See the best episodes of Bar Rescue below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Kuwtk Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-kuwtk-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 02:38:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-kuwtk-episodes/</guid>
      <description>A peek inside the exploits and privileged private lives of the blended Kardashian-Jenner family, including sisters Kim, Kourtney and Khloé. See the best episodes of Kuwtk below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Fear Factor Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-fear-factor-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 14:25:03 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-fear-factor-episodes/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Imagine a world where your greatest fears become reality.&amp;rdquo; In each pulse-racing &amp;ldquo;Fear Factor&amp;rdquo; episode, contestants recruited across the country battle in extreme stunts. These stunts are designed to challenge the contestants both physically and mentally. If a player is too afraid to complete or fail a stunt, the player is eliminated. If they succeed, they are one step closer to the grand prize: $50,000. See the best episodes of Fear Factor below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Running Man Funniest Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/running-man-funniest-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 14:14:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/running-man-funniest-episodes/</guid>
      <description>Running Man has one or more episodes streaming with subscription on Prime Video, and available for purchase on Prime Video. It has 297 episodes over 1 season. Running Man is still airing with no announced date for the next episode or season. See the best episodes of Running Man below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Episodes of the First 48</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-the-first-48/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 13:49:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-the-first-48/</guid>
      <description>The First 48 follows detectives from around the country during these first critical hours as they race against time to find the suspect. Gritty and fast-paced, it takes viewers behind the scenes of real-life investigations with unprecedented access to crime scenes, autopsies, forensic processing, and interrogations. See The First 48 best episodes below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Episodes of Married at First Sight</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-married-at-first-sight/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 13:22:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-married-at-first-sight/</guid>
      <description>A group of singles agree to marry partners chosen for them by a team of relationship experts. Looking forward to a perfect match, they meet their mates for the first time on their wedding day. Matchmaker experts arrange marriages between strangers using social science. See best Married at First Sight episodes below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Undercover Boss Episodes Us</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-undercover-boss-episodes-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 09:56:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-undercover-boss-episodes-us/</guid>
      <description>Reality series that follows high-level executives as they slip anonymously into the rank-and-file of their own organizations. Each week, a different leader will sacrifice the comfort of their corner office for an undercover mission to examine the inner workings of their operation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Episodes of Beyond Scared Straight</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-beyond-scared-straight/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 02:54:55 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-beyond-scared-straight/</guid>
      <description>Observing programs for troubled teens in which inmates reveal the realities of prison life in the hope of deterring them from a life of crime. Each hourlong episode follows a handful of at-risk teenagers as they attend a program, which includes an intensive one-day session in a prison. A month later, the teens are asked what, if any, lasting impressions the program had on them. Some change their ways following the experience while others continue down the same path they were on before.See the best Beyond Scared Straight episodes below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Episodes of Catfish</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-catfish/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 13:43:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-catfish/</guid>
      <description>Nev and his co-hosts &amp;ndash; from Max to Kamie to celebrity guests &amp;ndash; help people in dubious online relationships track down their baes IRL so they can sort out what&amp;rsquo;s fact and what&amp;rsquo;s fiction. The show is about the truths and lies of online dating. See the best episodes of Catfish below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Episodes of Impractical Jokers</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-impractical-jokers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 09:18:38 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-impractical-jokers/</guid>
      <description>Four comedians and lifelong friends compete to embarrass each other out amongst the general public with a series of hilarious and outrageous dares. When Sal, Joe, Q, and Murr challenge each other to say or do something, they have to do it. And if they refuse, they lose. At the end of every episode, the biggest loser must endure a punishment of epic proportions. See some of the best Impractical Jokers episodes below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Shark Tank Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-shark-tank-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 08:11:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-shark-tank-episodes/</guid>
      <description>Aspiring entrepreneurs present various business ideas to moguls known as sharks in the hope of landing an investment. See the best episodes of shark tank below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Ghost Adventures Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-ghost-adventures-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-ghost-adventures-episodes/</guid>
      <description>Paranormal investigator Zak Bagans and his crew, Nick Groff and Aaron Goodwin, search for haunted locations both domestically and internationally. During their investigations, Zak and crew acquaint themselves with the general area; interview locals about the hauntings; and go face-to-face with the evil spirits who reportedly haunt these locations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Episodes of Kitchen Nightmares</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-kitchen-nightmares/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-kitchen-nightmares/</guid>
      <description>Gordon Ramsay&amp;rsquo;s British series gets made over for American Television. The protagonist of this series is the world renowned Chef Gordon Ramsay. In this series, Ramsay will hit the road to help many a struggling restaurant find the path to success in just one week. See the best episodes of Kitchen Nightmares.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
