<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>anime on </title>
    <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/genres/anime/</link>
    <description>Recent content in anime on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 19:34:39 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bestepisodes.xyz/genres/anime/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Best KissxSis Episodes List</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-kissxsis-episodes-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 19:34:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-kissxsis-episodes-list/</guid>
      <description>The story begins with Keita Suminoe, a male third-year junior-high school student studying for his high school entrance exams. He is living in a home with his older twin stepsisters, Ako and Riko, who share no blood relation to him, and they help him prepare for his exams. Even though he initially dislikes himself for it, he begins to become attracted to his two step-sisters, and his two parents encourage him to eventually get married to one of them. KissXsis is a Japanese ecchi anime that was first aired in 2010. See the best episodes of KissXsis below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Bleach Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-bleach-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 09:15:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-bleach-episodes/</guid>
      <description>For as long as he can remember, Ichigo Kurosaki has been able to see ghosts. But when he meets Rukia, a Soul Reaper who battles evil spirits known as Hollows, he finds his life is changed forever. Now, with a newfound wealth of spiritual energy, Ichigo discovers his true calling: to protect the living and the dead from evil. Bleach is a Japanese action fantasy anime that was first aired in 2004. See the best episodes of Bleach below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Sweet Punishment: I&#39;m the Guard&#39;s Personal Pet Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-sweet-punishment-im-the-guards-personal-pet-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 22:20:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-sweet-punishment-im-the-guards-personal-pet-episodes/</guid>
      <description>The story is set in a prison in the near future. It revolves around Hina Saotome, imprisoned despite her innocence, and the elegant yet sadistic guard Aki Myoujin. Hina&amp;rsquo;s heart and body are at the mercy of Myoujin&amp;rsquo;s heartless yet sweet domination from physical examinations to lovers&#39; prison visits. Sweet Punishment is a Japanese romance fantasy anime that was first aired on Tokyo MX. See the best episodes of Sweet Punishment below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best My Hero Academia Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-my-hero-academia-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 18:40:02 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-my-hero-academia-episodes/</guid>
      <description>In a world where eighty percent of the population has some kind of super-powered Quirk, Izuku was unlucky enough to be born completely normal. But that won’t stop him from enrolling in a prestigious hero academy. Now, he’ll get his first taste of brutal rivalry from other schools as he braves the cutthroat, no-holds-barred provisional license exam. My Hero Academia is a Japanese action fantasy anime that was first aired in 2016 on MBS. See the best episodes of My Hero Academia below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Fairy Tail Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-fairy-tail-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 16:40:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-fairy-tail-episodes/</guid>
      <description>Lucy is a 17-year-old girl, who wants to be a full-fledged mage. One day when visiting Harujion Town, she meets Natsu, a young man who gets sick easily by any type of transportation. But Natsu isn&amp;rsquo;t just any ordinary kid, he&amp;rsquo;s a member of one of the world&amp;rsquo;s most infamous mage guilds: Fairy Tail. Fairy Tail is a Japanese adventure and fantasy anime that was first aired in 2009 on Tv Tokyo network. See the best episodes of Fairy Tail below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best One Piece Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-one-piece-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 15:24:38 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-one-piece-episodes/</guid>
      <description>Years ago, the fearsome pirate king Gol D. Roger was executed, leaving a huge pile of treasure and the famous &amp;lsquo;One Piece&amp;rsquo; behind. Whoever claims the &amp;lsquo;One Piece&amp;rsquo; will be named the new pirate king. Monkey D. Luffy, a boy who consumed one of the &amp;lsquo;Devil&amp;rsquo;s Fruits&amp;rsquo;, has it in his head that he&amp;rsquo;ll follow in the footsteps of his idol, the pirate Shanks, and find the One Piece. It helps, of course, that his body has the properties of rubber and he&amp;rsquo;s surrounded by a bevy of skilled fighters and thieves to help him along the way. Monkey D. Luffy brings a bunch of his crew followed by, Roronoa Zoro, Nami, Usopp, Sanji, Tony-Tony Chopper, Nico Robin, Franky, and Brook. They will do anything to get the One Piece and become King of the Pirates! One Piece is a Japanese action and adventure anime that was first aired in 1999. See the best episodes of One Piece below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Attack on Titan Episodes List</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-attack-on-titan-episodes-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 13:18:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-attack-on-titan-episodes-list/</guid>
      <description>Several hundred years ago, humans were nearly exterminated by Titans. Titans are typically several stories tall, seem to have no intelligence, devour human beings and, worst of all, seem to do it for the pleasure rather than as a food source. A small percentage of humanity survived by walling themselves in a city protected by extremely high walls, even taller than the biggest Titans. Flash forward to the present and the city has not seen a Titan in over 100 years. Teenage boy Eren and his foster sister Mikasa witness something horrific as the city walls are destroyed by a Colossal Titan that appears out of thin air. As the smaller Titans flood the city, the two kids watch in horror as their mother is eaten alive. Eren vows that he will murder every single Titan and take revenge for all of mankind.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
