<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>nickelodeon on </title>
    <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/network/nickelodeon/</link>
    <description>Recent content in nickelodeon on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 14:01:38 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bestepisodes.xyz/network/nickelodeon/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Best SpongeBob Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-spongebob-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 14:01:38 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-spongebob-episodes/</guid>
      <description>Deep down in the Pacific Ocean in the subterranean city of Bikini Bottom lives a square yellow sponge named SpongeBob SquarePants. SpongeBob lives in a pineapple with his pet snail, Gary, loves his job as a fry cook at the Krusty Krab, and has a knack for getting into all kinds of trouble without really trying. When he&amp;rsquo;s not getting on the nerves of his cranky next door neighbor Squidward, SpongeBob can usually be found smack in the middle of all sorts of strange situations with his best buddy, the simple yet lovable starfish, Patrick, or his thrill-seeking surfer-girl squirrel pal, Sandy Cheeks. Spongebob Squarepants is an animated comedy tv-series that was first aired in 1999. See the best episodes of SpongeBob below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Icarly Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-icarly-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 10:36:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-icarly-episodes/</guid>
      <description>Watch Carly, Sam, and Freddie, as they try to balance their everyday 8th grade lives with their newfound fame managing and starring in the most awesome show on the web. iCarly is an American teen sitcom that was first aired in 2007. See the best episodes of iCarly below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Drake and Josh Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-drake-and-josh-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 14:38:50 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-drake-and-josh-episodes/</guid>
      <description>15-year-old Drake and Josh are schoolmates, but not close friends. Drake views Josh as weird and a bit of a goof. So, imagine Drake&amp;rsquo;s shock when he finds out that this goof is about to become his new step-brother and roommate when his mother marries Josh&amp;rsquo;s father. A spin off of The Amanda Show. See the best episodes of Drake and Josh tv-show below.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
