<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>fox on </title>
    <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/network/fox/</link>
    <description>Recent content in fox on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 05:31:25 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bestepisodes.xyz/network/fox/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Best Episodes of Bones</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-bones/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 05:31:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-bones/</guid>
      <description>Dr. Temperance Brennan and her colleagues at the Jeffersonian&amp;rsquo;s Medico-Legal Lab assist Special Agent Seeley Booth with murder investigations when the remains are so badly decomposed, burned or destroyed that the standard identification methods are useless. See the best Bones episodes below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best That &#39;70s Show Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-that-70s-show-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 16:27:55 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-that-70s-show-episodes/</guid>
      <description>Crank up the 8-track and flash back to a time when platform shoes and puka shells were all the rage in this hilarious retro-sitcom. For Eric, Kelso, Jackie, Hyde, Donna and Fez, a group of high school teens who spend most of their time hanging out in Eric’s basement, life in the ‘70s isn’t always so groovy. But between trying to figure out the meaning of life, avoiding their parents, and dealing with out-of-control hormones, they’ve learned one thing for sure: they’ll always get by with a little help from their friends. See the best episodes of That &amp;rsquo;70s Show series below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best American Dad Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-american-dad-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 16:02:18 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-american-dad-episodes/</guid>
      <description>The series focuses on an eccentric motley crew that is the Smith family and their three housemates: Father, husband, and breadwinner Stan Smith; his better half housewife, Francine Smith; their college-aged daughter, Hayley Smith; and their high-school-aged son, Steve Smith. Outside of the Smith family, there are three additional main characters, including Hayley&amp;rsquo;s boyfriend turned husband, Jeff Fischer; the family&amp;rsquo;s man-in-a-goldfish-body pet, Klaus; and most notably the family&amp;rsquo;s zany alien, Roger, who is full of masquerades, brazenness, and shocking antics. See the best episodes of American Dad below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Episodes of New Girl</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-new-girl/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 12:51:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-new-girl/</guid>
      <description>Jessica Day is an offbeat and adorable girl in her late 20s who, after a bad breakup, moves in with three single guys. Goofy, positive, vulnerable and honest to a fault, Jess has faith in people, even when she shouldn&amp;rsquo;t. Although she&amp;rsquo;s dorky and awkward, she&amp;rsquo;s comfortable in her own skin. More prone to friendships with women, she&amp;rsquo;s not used to hanging with the boys—especially at home. See the best New Girl episodes below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bobs Burgers Best Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/bobs-burgers-best-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 10:31:50 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/bobs-burgers-best-episodes/</guid>
      <description>Bob&amp;rsquo;s Burgers follows a third-generation restaurateur, Bob, as he runs Bob&amp;rsquo;s Burgers with the help of his wife and their three kids. Bob and his quirky family have big ideas about burgers, but fall short on service and sophistication. Despite the greasy counters, lousy location and a dearth of customers, Bob and his family are determined to make Bob&amp;rsquo;s Burgers &amp;lsquo;grand re-re-re-opening&amp;rsquo; a success. See best Bob&amp;rsquo;s Burgers Episodes below to binge-watch on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Episodes of Family Guy</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-family-guy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 12:14:27 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-family-guy/</guid>
      <description>Sick, twisted, politically incorrect and Freakin&#39; Sweet animated series featuring the adventures of the dysfunctional Griffin family. Bumbling Peter and long-suffering Lois have three kids. Stewie (a brilliant but sadistic baby bent on killing his mother and taking over the world), Meg (the oldest, and is the most unpopular girl in town) and Chris (the middle kid, he&amp;rsquo;s not very bright but has a passion for movies). The final member of the family is Brian - a talking dog and much more than a pet, he keeps Stewie in check whilst sipping Martinis and sorting through his own life issues. See the best Family Guy episodes below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Episodes of Kitchen Nightmares</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-kitchen-nightmares/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-kitchen-nightmares/</guid>
      <description>Gordon Ramsay&amp;rsquo;s British series gets made over for American Television. The protagonist of this series is the world renowned Chef Gordon Ramsay. In this series, Ramsay will hit the road to help many a struggling restaurant find the path to success in just one week. See the best episodes of Kitchen Nightmares.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
