<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ane on </title>
    <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/network/ane/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ane on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 13:49:29 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bestepisodes.xyz/network/ane/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Best Episodes of The First 48</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-the-first-48/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 13:49:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-the-first-48/</guid>
      <description>The First 48 follows detectives from around the country during these first critical hours as they race against time to find the suspect. Gritty and fast-paced, it takes viewers behind the scenes of real-life investigations with unprecedented access to crime scenes, autopsies, forensic processing, and interrogations. See The First 48 best episodes below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Intervention Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-intervention-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 10:48:02 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-intervention-episodes/</guid>
      <description>People whose uncontrollable addiction to drugs, alcohol or compulsive behavior has brought them to the brink of destruction and has devastated their family and friends are presented with a life-changing opportunity of intervention and rehab. Each addict must confront their darkest demons in order to begin their journey to recovery in the hopes that they can turn their lives around before it’s too late. See best episodes of Intervention series below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Worst Episodes of Hoarders</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/worst-episodes-of-hoarders/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 03:20:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/worst-episodes-of-hoarders/</guid>
      <description>Each episode of Hoarders is a fascinating look inside the lives of two different people whose inability to part with their belongings is so out of control that they are on the verge of a personal crisis. See the worst episodes of Hoarders below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Episodes of Beyond Scared Straight</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-beyond-scared-straight/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 02:54:55 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-beyond-scared-straight/</guid>
      <description>Observing programs for troubled teens in which inmates reveal the realities of prison life in the hope of deterring them from a life of crime. Each hourlong episode follows a handful of at-risk teenagers as they attend a program, which includes an intensive one-day session in a prison. A month later, the teens are asked what, if any, lasting impressions the program had on them. Some change their ways following the experience while others continue down the same path they were on before.See the best Beyond Scared Straight episodes below.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
