<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>mystery on </title>
    <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/genres/mystery/</link>
    <description>Recent content in mystery on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 18:10:17 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bestepisodes.xyz/genres/mystery/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Best Law and Order Svu Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-law-and-order-svu-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 18:10:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-law-and-order-svu-episodes/</guid>
      <description>In the criminal justice system, sexually-based offenses are considered especially heinous. In New York City, the dedicated detectives who investigate these vicious felonies are members of an elite squad known as the Special Victims Unit. These are their stories. Law and Order: Special Victims Unit is an American mystery crime tv-series that was first aired in 1999. See the best episodes of Law and Order: Special Victims Unit below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best the 100 Episodes List</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-the-100-episodes-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 22:38:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-the-100-episodes-list/</guid>
      <description>100 years in the future, when the Earth has been abandoned due to radioactivity, the last surviving humans live on an ark orbiting the planet — but the ark won&amp;rsquo;t last forever. So the repressive regime picks 100 expendable juvenile delinquents to send down to Earth to see if the planet is still habitable. The 100 is an American fantasy mystery tv-series that was first aired in 2004. See the best episodes of The 100 below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NCIS Best Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/ncis-best-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 16:53:43 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/ncis-best-episodes/</guid>
      <description>From murder and espionage to terrorism and stolen submarines, a team of special agents investigates any crime that has a shred of evidence connected to Navy and Marine Corps personnel, regardless of rank or position. NCIS is an American comedy mystery tv-series that first aired in 2003 on CBS. See the best NCIS episodes below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Arrow Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-arrow-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 11:46:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-arrow-episodes/</guid>
      <description>Spoiled billionaire playboy Oliver Queen is missing and presumed dead when his yacht is lost at sea. He returns five years later a changed man, determined to clean up the city as a hooded vigilante armed with a bow. Arrow is an American fantasy mystery tv-series that was first aired in 2012 on The CW. See the best episodes of Arrow below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Episodes of the Vampire Diaries</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-the-vampire-diaries/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 07:18:18 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-the-vampire-diaries/</guid>
      <description>The story of two vampire brothers obsessed with the same girl, who bears a striking resemblance to the beautiful but ruthless vampire they knew and loved in 1864. The Vampire Diaries is an American teen romance supernatural tv-series that was first aired in 2009. See The Vampire Diaries best episodes below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Episodes of Law and Order</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-law-and-order/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 10:08:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-law-and-order/</guid>
      <description>Follows a crime (usually a murder), usually adapted from current headlines, from two separate vantage points, the police investigation and the prosecution in court. Law and Order is an American police and legal drama tv series that was first premiered in 1990. See the best Law and Order episodes below to binge-watch on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Mentalist Best Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/the-mentalist-best-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 12:40:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/the-mentalist-best-episodes/</guid>
      <description>Patrick Jane, a former celebrity psychic medium, uses his razor sharp skills of observation and expertise at &amp;ldquo;reading&amp;rdquo; people to solve serious crimes with the California Bureau of Investigation. See the best episodes of The Mentalist below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Criminal Minds Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-criminal-minds-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 10:20:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-criminal-minds-episodes/</guid>
      <description>An elite team of FBI profilers analyze the country&amp;rsquo;s most twisted criminal minds, anticipating their next moves before they strike again. The Behavioral Analysis Unit&amp;rsquo;s most experienced agent is David Rossi, a founding member of the BAU who returns to help the team solve new cases. See the best episodes of Criminal Minds below.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
