<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cbs on </title>
    <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/network/cbs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in cbs on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 21:13:36 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bestepisodes.xyz/network/cbs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Best Tales From the Darkside Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-tales-from-the-darkside-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 21:13:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-tales-from-the-darkside-episodes/</guid>
      <description>Tales from the Darkside is an anthology horror TV series created by George A. Romero; it was released in 1984. Similar to Amazing Stories, The Twilight Zone, Night Gallery, The Outer Limits, Tales From The Crypt, and Lee Martin&amp;rsquo;s The Midnight Hour, each episode was an individual short story that ended with a plot twist. The series&#39; episodes spanned the genres of horror, science fiction, and fantasy, and some episodes featured elements of black comedy or more lighthearted themes. Tales from the Darkside is an American thriller science-fiction tv-series that first aired in 1984 and ran till 1988. See the best episodes of Tales from the Darkside below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Episodes of Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-alfred-hitchcock-presents/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 19:12:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-alfred-hitchcock-presents/</guid>
      <description>Alfred Hitchcock Presents is an American television anthology series hosted by Alfred Hitchcock. The series featured dramas, thrillers, and mysteries. By the time the show premiered on October 2, 1955, Hitchcock had been directing films for over three decades. Time magazine named Alfred Hitchcock Presents one of The 100 Best TV Shows of All-TIME. A series of literary anthologies with the running title Alfred Hitchcock Presents were issued to capitalize on the success of the television series. One volume, devoted to stories that censors wouldn&amp;rsquo;t allow to be adapted for the TV series, was entitled Alfred Hitchcock Presents: Stories They Wouldn&amp;rsquo;t Let Me Do on TV—though eventually several of the stories collected were adapted. See the best episodes of Alfred Hitchcock below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Perry Mason Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-perry-mason-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 10:54:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-perry-mason-episodes/</guid>
      <description>The cases of master criminal defense attorney Perry Mason and his staff who handled the most difficult of cases in the aid of the innocent. Perry Mason is an American crime drama tv-series that was first aired in 1957. See the best episodes of Perry Mason Below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NCIS Best Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/ncis-best-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 16:53:43 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/ncis-best-episodes/</guid>
      <description>From murder and espionage to terrorism and stolen submarines, a team of special agents investigates any crime that has a shred of evidence connected to Navy and Marine Corps personnel, regardless of rank or position. NCIS is an American comedy mystery tv-series that first aired in 2003 on CBS. See the best NCIS episodes below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Episodes of The Big Bang Theory</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-big-bang-theory/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 14:13:02 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-big-bang-theory/</guid>
      <description>The sitcom is centered on five characters living in Pasadena, California: roommates Leonard Hofstadter and Sheldon Cooper; Penny, a waitress and aspiring actress who lives across the hall; and Leonard and Sheldon&amp;rsquo;s equally geeky and socially awkward friends and co-workers, mechanical engineer Howard Wolowitz and astrophysicist Raj Koothrappali. The geekiness and intellect of the four guys is contrasted for comic effect with Penny&amp;rsquo;s social skills and common sense. The Big Bang Theory is an American sitcom tv-series that was first aired in 2007 on CBS. See the best The Big Bang Theory episodes below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Undercover Boss Episodes Us</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-undercover-boss-episodes-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 09:56:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-undercover-boss-episodes-us/</guid>
      <description>Reality series that follows high-level executives as they slip anonymously into the rank-and-file of their own organizations. Each week, a different leader will sacrifice the comfort of their corner office for an undercover mission to examine the inner workings of their operation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Mentalist Best Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/the-mentalist-best-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 12:40:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/the-mentalist-best-episodes/</guid>
      <description>Patrick Jane, a former celebrity psychic medium, uses his razor sharp skills of observation and expertise at &amp;ldquo;reading&amp;rdquo; people to solve serious crimes with the California Bureau of Investigation. See the best episodes of The Mentalist below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Criminal Minds Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-criminal-minds-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 10:20:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-criminal-minds-episodes/</guid>
      <description>An elite team of FBI profilers analyze the country&amp;rsquo;s most twisted criminal minds, anticipating their next moves before they strike again. The Behavioral Analysis Unit&amp;rsquo;s most experienced agent is David Rossi, a founding member of the BAU who returns to help the team solve new cases. See the best episodes of Criminal Minds below.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
