<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>history on </title>
    <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/network/history/</link>
    <description>Recent content in history on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 23:21:37 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bestepisodes.xyz/network/history/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Best Alone Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-alone-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 23:21:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-alone-episodes/</guid>
      <description>Hardcore survivalists are put by themselves in the Vancouver Island wilderness, without camera crews, teams, or producers – on a single mission to stay alive for as long as possible. Alone is an American game-show documentary tv-series that was first aired in 2015. See the best episodes of Alone below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best History Channel Documentaries</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-history-channel-documentaries/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 10:46:43 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-history-channel-documentaries/</guid>
      <description>The History Channel is a satellite and cable TV channel, devoted mainly to historical events and persons. Programming covers a wide array of periods and topics, while similar topics are often organized into themed weeks or daily marathons. Subjects include military history, medieval history, the 19th, 20th, and 21st centuries, modern engineering, and historical biographies. See the best episodes of History Channel Documentaries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Forged in Fire Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-forged-in-fire-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 10:23:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-forged-in-fire-episodes/</guid>
      <description>Competitors re-create weapons from historical periods ranging from Japanese katanas to medieval broadswords to ancient throwing blades. Each entry is judged on its artistry as well as its functionality and accuracy. Forged in Fire is an American reality game-show tv-series that was first aired in 2015. See the best episodes of Forged in Fire below.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
