<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>animation on </title>
    <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/genres/animation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in animation on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2021 14:37:25 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bestepisodes.xyz/genres/animation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Best Funniest King of the Hill Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-funniest-king-of-the-hill-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2021 14:37:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-funniest-king-of-the-hill-episodes/</guid>
      <description>Set in Texas, this animated series follows the life of propane salesman Hank Hill, who lives with his overly confident substitute Spanish teacher wife Peggy, wannabe comedian son Bobby, and naive niece Luanne. Hank has conservative views about God, family, and country, but his values and ethics are often challenged by the situations he, his family, and his beer-drinking neighbors/buddies find themselves in. King of the Hill is an American animated sitcom that was first aired in 1997. See the best King of the hill episodes below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Gravity Falls Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-gravity-falls-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 22:49:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-gravity-falls-episodes/</guid>
      <description>Twin brother and sister Dipper and Mabel Pines are in for an unexpected adventure when they spend the summer helping their great uncle Stan run a tourist trap in the mysterious town of Gravity Falls, Oregon. Gravity Falls is an animated American comedy tv-series that was first aired in 2012. See the best episodes of Gravity Falls below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Kissxsis Episodes List</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-kissxsis-episodes-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 19:34:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-kissxsis-episodes-list/</guid>
      <description>The story begins with Keita Suminoe, a male third-year junior-high school student studying for his high school entrance exams. He is living in a home with his older twin stepsisters, Ako and Riko, who share no blood relation to him, and they help him prepare for his exams. Even though he initially dislikes himself for it, he begins to become attracted to his two step-sisters, and his two parents encourage him to eventually get married to one of them. KissXsis is a Japanese ecchi anime that was first aired in 2010. See the best episodes of KissXsis below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Gumball Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-gumball-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 09:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-gumball-episodes/</guid>
      <description>The life of Gumball Watterson, a 12-year old cat who attends middle school in Elmore. Accompanied by his pet, adoptive brother, and best friend Darwin Watterson, he frequently finds himself involved in various shenanigans around the city, during which he interacts with various family members: Anais, Richard, and Nicole Watterson, and other various citizens. The Amazing World of Gumball is a United Kingdom based cartoon tv-series that was first aired in 2011. See the best episodes of Gumball below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Bleach Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-bleach-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 09:15:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-bleach-episodes/</guid>
      <description>For as long as he can remember, Ichigo Kurosaki has been able to see ghosts. But when he meets Rukia, a Soul Reaper who battles evil spirits known as Hollows, he finds his life is changed forever. Now, with a newfound wealth of spiritual energy, Ichigo discovers his true calling: to protect the living and the dead from evil. Bleach is a Japanese action fantasy anime that was first aired in 2004. See the best episodes of Bleach below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Sweet Punishment: I&#39;m the Guard&#39;s Personal Pet Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-sweet-punishment-im-the-guards-personal-pet-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 22:20:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-sweet-punishment-im-the-guards-personal-pet-episodes/</guid>
      <description>The story is set in a prison in the near future. It revolves around Hina Saotome, imprisoned despite her innocence, and the elegant yet sadistic guard Aki Myoujin. Hina&amp;rsquo;s heart and body are at the mercy of Myoujin&amp;rsquo;s heartless yet sweet domination from physical examinations to lovers&#39; prison visits. Sweet Punishment is a Japanese romance fantasy anime that was first aired on Tokyo MX. See the best episodes of Sweet Punishment below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best My Hero Academia Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-my-hero-academia-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 18:40:02 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-my-hero-academia-episodes/</guid>
      <description>In a world where eighty percent of the population has some kind of super-powered Quirk, Izuku was unlucky enough to be born completely normal. But that won’t stop him from enrolling in a prestigious hero academy. Now, he’ll get his first taste of brutal rivalry from other schools as he braves the cutthroat, no-holds-barred provisional license exam. My Hero Academia is a Japanese action fantasy anime that was first aired in 2016 on MBS. See the best episodes of My Hero Academia below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Fairy Tail Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-fairy-tail-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 16:40:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-fairy-tail-episodes/</guid>
      <description>Lucy is a 17-year-old girl, who wants to be a full-fledged mage. One day when visiting Harujion Town, she meets Natsu, a young man who gets sick easily by any type of transportation. But Natsu isn&amp;rsquo;t just any ordinary kid, he&amp;rsquo;s a member of one of the world&amp;rsquo;s most infamous mage guilds: Fairy Tail. Fairy Tail is a Japanese adventure and fantasy anime that was first aired in 2009 on Tv Tokyo network. See the best episodes of Fairy Tail below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Three Stooges Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-three-stooges-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 16:26:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-three-stooges-episodes/</guid>
      <description>The Three Stooges were an American vaudeville and comedy team active from 1922 until 1970, best known for their 190 short subject films by Columbia Pictures that have been regularly airing on television since 1958. Their hallmark was physical farce and slapstick. In films, the stooges were commonly known by their actual first names. There were a total of six stooges over the act&amp;rsquo;s run (with only three active at any given time), but Moe Howard and Larry Fine were the mainstays throughout the ensemble&amp;rsquo;s nearly fifty-year run. The Three Stooges are American short subject films that ran from 1934 to 1959. See the best episodes of The Three Stooges below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best One Piece Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-one-piece-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 15:24:38 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-one-piece-episodes/</guid>
      <description>Years ago, the fearsome pirate king Gol D. Roger was executed, leaving a huge pile of treasure and the famous &amp;lsquo;One Piece&amp;rsquo; behind. Whoever claims the &amp;lsquo;One Piece&amp;rsquo; will be named the new pirate king. Monkey D. Luffy, a boy who consumed one of the &amp;lsquo;Devil&amp;rsquo;s Fruits&amp;rsquo;, has it in his head that he&amp;rsquo;ll follow in the footsteps of his idol, the pirate Shanks, and find the One Piece. It helps, of course, that his body has the properties of rubber and he&amp;rsquo;s surrounded by a bevy of skilled fighters and thieves to help him along the way. Monkey D. Luffy brings a bunch of his crew followed by, Roronoa Zoro, Nami, Usopp, Sanji, Tony-Tony Chopper, Nico Robin, Franky, and Brook. They will do anything to get the One Piece and become King of the Pirates! One Piece is a Japanese action and adventure anime that was first aired in 1999. See the best episodes of One Piece below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best SpongeBob Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-spongebob-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 14:01:38 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-spongebob-episodes/</guid>
      <description>Deep down in the Pacific Ocean in the subterranean city of Bikini Bottom lives a square yellow sponge named SpongeBob SquarePants. SpongeBob lives in a pineapple with his pet snail, Gary, loves his job as a fry cook at the Krusty Krab, and has a knack for getting into all kinds of trouble without really trying. When he&amp;rsquo;s not getting on the nerves of his cranky next door neighbor Squidward, SpongeBob can usually be found smack in the middle of all sorts of strange situations with his best buddy, the simple yet lovable starfish, Patrick, or his thrill-seeking surfer-girl squirrel pal, Sandy Cheeks. Spongebob Squarepants is an animated comedy tv-series that was first aired in 1999. See the best episodes of SpongeBob below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Frasier Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-frasier-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 11:14:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-frasier-episodes/</guid>
      <description>After many years spent at the “Cheers” bar, Frasier moves back home to Seattle to work as a radio psychiatrist after his policeman father gets shot in the hip on duty. Frasier is an American comedy tv-series that was first aired in 1993 on NBC. See the best episodes of Frasier below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Phineas and Ferb Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-phineas-and-ferb-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 10:20:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-phineas-and-ferb-episodes/</guid>
      <description>Each day, two kindhearted suburban stepbrothers on summer vacation embark on some grand new project, which annoys their controlling sister, Candace, who tries to bust them. Meanwhile, their pet platypus plots against evil Dr. Doofenshmirtz. Phineas and Ferb is an American animated comedy tv-series that was first aired in 2007. See the best episodes of Phineas and Ferb below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Attack on Titan Episodes List</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-attack-on-titan-episodes-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 13:18:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-attack-on-titan-episodes-list/</guid>
      <description>Several hundred years ago, humans were nearly exterminated by Titans. Titans are typically several stories tall, seem to have no intelligence, devour human beings and, worst of all, seem to do it for the pleasure rather than as a food source. A small percentage of humanity survived by walling themselves in a city protected by extremely high walls, even taller than the biggest Titans. Flash forward to the present and the city has not seen a Titan in over 100 years. Teenage boy Eren and his foster sister Mikasa witness something horrific as the city walls are destroyed by a Colossal Titan that appears out of thin air. As the smaller Titans flood the city, the two kids watch in horror as their mother is eaten alive. Eren vows that he will murder every single Titan and take revenge for all of mankind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Episodes of South Park</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-south-park/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 09:12:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-south-park/</guid>
      <description>Follows the misadventures of four irreverent grade-schoolers in the quiet, dysfunctional town of South Park, Colorado. South Park is an American animated sitcom that was first aired in 1997. See the best South Park episodes below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Tom and Jerry Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-tom-and-jerry-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 08:26:40 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-tom-and-jerry-episodes/</guid>
      <description>Tom and Jerry is a series of theatrical animated cartoon films created by William Hanna and Joseph Barbera for Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer, centering on a rivalry between a cat and a mouse whose chases include slapstick comedy. Tom and Jerry is an American animated comedy tv-series that was first aired in 1940. See the best episodes of Tom and Jerry below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Peepoodo Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-peepoodo-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 17:00:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-peepoodo-episodes/</guid>
      <description>A sex education series for teenagers, Peepoodo and his friend explore sexuality in all forms and no taboos. A positive message on sexuality, that is unrestrained and without prejudices - culminating into one single message: Tolerance. See the best episodes of Peepoodo below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best American Dad Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-american-dad-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 16:02:18 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-american-dad-episodes/</guid>
      <description>The series focuses on an eccentric motley crew that is the Smith family and their three housemates: Father, husband, and breadwinner Stan Smith; his better half housewife, Francine Smith; their college-aged daughter, Hayley Smith; and their high-school-aged son, Steve Smith. Outside of the Smith family, there are three additional main characters, including Hayley&amp;rsquo;s boyfriend turned husband, Jeff Fischer; the family&amp;rsquo;s man-in-a-goldfish-body pet, Klaus; and most notably the family&amp;rsquo;s zany alien, Roger, who is full of masquerades, brazenness, and shocking antics. See the best episodes of American Dad below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Regular Show&#39;s Best Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/regular-show-best-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 14:01:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/regular-show-best-episodes/</guid>
      <description>Two bored groundskeepers, Mordecai (a six-foot-tall blue jay) and Rigby (a hyperactive raccoon) are best friends who spend their days trying to entertain themselves by any means necessary, much to the displeasure of their boss. Their everyday pursuits often lead to things spiraling out of control and into the surreal. See the best Regular Show episodes below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Episodes of New Girl</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-new-girl/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 12:51:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-new-girl/</guid>
      <description>Jessica Day is an offbeat and adorable girl in her late 20s who, after a bad breakup, moves in with three single guys. Goofy, positive, vulnerable and honest to a fault, Jess has faith in people, even when she shouldn&amp;rsquo;t. Although she&amp;rsquo;s dorky and awkward, she&amp;rsquo;s comfortable in her own skin. More prone to friendships with women, she&amp;rsquo;s not used to hanging with the boys—especially at home. See the best New Girl episodes below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Workaholics Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-workaholics-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 11:24:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-workaholics-episodes/</guid>
      <description>The misadventures of three recent college dropouts, roommates, and co-workers at a telemarketing company and their drug dealer. See the best episodes of Workaholics tv-show below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bobs Burgers Best Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/bobs-burgers-best-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 10:31:50 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/bobs-burgers-best-episodes/</guid>
      <description>Bob&amp;rsquo;s Burgers follows a third-generation restaurateur, Bob, as he runs Bob&amp;rsquo;s Burgers with the help of his wife and their three kids. Bob and his quirky family have big ideas about burgers, but fall short on service and sophistication. Despite the greasy counters, lousy location and a dearth of customers, Bob and his family are determined to make Bob&amp;rsquo;s Burgers &amp;lsquo;grand re-re-re-opening&amp;rsquo; a success. See best Bob&amp;rsquo;s Burgers Episodes below to binge-watch on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Episodes of Family Guy</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-family-guy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 12:14:27 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-family-guy/</guid>
      <description>Sick, twisted, politically incorrect and Freakin&#39; Sweet animated series featuring the adventures of the dysfunctional Griffin family. Bumbling Peter and long-suffering Lois have three kids. Stewie (a brilliant but sadistic baby bent on killing his mother and taking over the world), Meg (the oldest, and is the most unpopular girl in town) and Chris (the middle kid, he&amp;rsquo;s not very bright but has a passion for movies). The final member of the family is Brian - a talking dog and much more than a pet, he keeps Stewie in check whilst sipping Martinis and sorting through his own life issues. See the best Family Guy episodes below.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
