<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>science-fiction on </title>
    <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/genres/science-fiction/</link>
    <description>Recent content in science-fiction on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 21:13:36 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bestepisodes.xyz/genres/science-fiction/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Best Tales From the Darkside Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-tales-from-the-darkside-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 21:13:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-tales-from-the-darkside-episodes/</guid>
      <description>Tales from the Darkside is an anthology horror TV series created by George A. Romero; it was released in 1984. Similar to Amazing Stories, The Twilight Zone, Night Gallery, The Outer Limits, Tales From The Crypt, and Lee Martin&amp;rsquo;s The Midnight Hour, each episode was an individual short story that ended with a plot twist. The series&#39; episodes spanned the genres of horror, science fiction, and fantasy, and some episodes featured elements of black comedy or more lighthearted themes. Tales from the Darkside is an American thriller science-fiction tv-series that first aired in 1984 and ran till 1988. See the best episodes of Tales from the Darkside below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Outer Limits Best Episodes (1995)</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/outer-limits-best-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 07:34:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/outer-limits-best-episodes/</guid>
      <description>The Outer Limits is an anthology series of distinct story episodes, sometimes with a plot twist at the end. Unlike the original incarnation of the series, which was a pure anthology with each episode completely unrelated to the others, the revival series maintained an anthology format, but occasionally featured recurring story elements that were often tied together during season-finale clip shows. The Outer Limits is an American science horror anthology tv-series that was first aired in 1995. See the best episodes of The Outer Limits below.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
