<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>documentary on </title>
    <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/genres/documentary/</link>
    <description>Recent content in documentary on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 15:06:21 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bestepisodes.xyz/genres/documentary/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Best Dateline Nbc Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-dateline-nbc-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 15:06:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-dateline-nbc-episodes/</guid>
      <description>Dateline NBC, or simply Dateline, is a weekly American television newsmagazine series. It was previously the network&amp;rsquo;s flagship newsmagazine, but now focuses mainly on true crime stories with only occasional editions that focus on other topics. Dateline NBC is an American documentary tv-series that was first aired in 1992. See the best episodes of Dateline NBC below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best I Am a Killer Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-i-am-a-killer-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 10:30:20 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-i-am-a-killer-episodes/</guid>
      <description>Death row inmates convicted of capital murder give a firsthand account of their crimes in this documentary series. I am a Killer is an American crime documentary series that was first aired in 2018 on Netflix. See the best episodes of I Am a Killer below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Doomsday Preppers Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-doomsday-preppers-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 11:10:52 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-doomsday-preppers-episodes/</guid>
      <description>Doomsday Preppers is an American reality television series that airs on the National Geographic Channel. Dräger Equipment, Wise Food Storage Company and the United States Gold Bureau are sponsors of the show. Doomsday Preppers is an American reality documentary tv-series that was first aired in 2011 on National Geographic. See the best episodes of Doomsday Preppers below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mythbusters Best Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/mythbusters-best-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 11:01:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/mythbusters-best-episodes/</guid>
      <description>MythBusters is a science entertainment television program created and produced by Australia&amp;rsquo;s Beyond Television Productions for the Discovery Channel. The show&amp;rsquo;s hosts, special effects experts Adam Savage and Jamie Hyneman, use elements of the scientific method to test the validity of rumors, myths, movie scenes, adages, Internet videos, and news stories. Mythbusters is an American documentary series that was first aired in 2003. See the best episodes of Mythbusters below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best History Channel Documentaries</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-history-channel-documentaries/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 10:46:43 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-history-channel-documentaries/</guid>
      <description>The History Channel is a satellite and cable TV channel, devoted mainly to historical events and persons. Programming covers a wide array of periods and topics, while similar topics are often organized into themed weeks or daily marathons. Subjects include military history, medieval history, the 19th, 20th, and 21st centuries, modern engineering, and historical biographies. See the best episodes of History Channel Documentaries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Intervention Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-intervention-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 10:48:02 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-intervention-episodes/</guid>
      <description>People whose uncontrollable addiction to drugs, alcohol or compulsive behavior has brought them to the brink of destruction and has devastated their family and friends are presented with a life-changing opportunity of intervention and rehab. Each addict must confront their darkest demons in order to begin their journey to recovery in the hopes that they can turn their lives around before it’s too late. See best episodes of Intervention series below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Worst Episodes of Hoarders</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/worst-episodes-of-hoarders/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 03:20:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/worst-episodes-of-hoarders/</guid>
      <description>Each episode of Hoarders is a fascinating look inside the lives of two different people whose inability to part with their belongings is so out of control that they are on the verge of a personal crisis. See the worst episodes of Hoarders below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best River Monster Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-river-monsters-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 13:12:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-river-monsters-episodes/</guid>
      <description>Extreme angler Jeremy Wade is on the hunt for fish with a taste for human flesh. This rip-roaring ride mixes action and adventure with mysteries, edge-of-the-seat chase and a battle of wills between man and nature. The series was first premiered in 2009 that follows the biologist Jeremy Wade on his adventures with the river monsters around the world. See best episodes of River Monsters below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Ghost Adventures Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-ghost-adventures-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-ghost-adventures-episodes/</guid>
      <description>Paranormal investigator Zak Bagans and his crew, Nick Groff and Aaron Goodwin, search for haunted locations both domestically and internationally. During their investigations, Zak and crew acquaint themselves with the general area; interview locals about the hauntings; and go face-to-face with the evil spirits who reportedly haunt these locations.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
