<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>nbc on </title>
    <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/network/nbc/</link>
    <description>Recent content in nbc on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 22:51:50 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bestepisodes.xyz/network/nbc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Best Episodes of Er</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-er/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 22:51:50 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-er/</guid>
      <description>ER explores the inner workings of an urban teaching hospital and the critical issues faced by the dedicated physicians and staff of its overburdened emergency room. ER is an American drama tv-series that was first aired in 1994. See the best ER episodes below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Dateline Nbc Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-dateline-nbc-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 15:06:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-dateline-nbc-episodes/</guid>
      <description>Dateline NBC, or simply Dateline, is a weekly American television newsmagazine series. It was previously the network&amp;rsquo;s flagship newsmagazine, but now focuses mainly on true crime stories with only occasional editions that focus on other topics. Dateline NBC is an American documentary tv-series that was first aired in 1992. See the best episodes of Dateline NBC below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Frasier Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-frasier-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 11:14:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-frasier-episodes/</guid>
      <description>After many years spent at the “Cheers” bar, Frasier moves back home to Seattle to work as a radio psychiatrist after his policeman father gets shot in the hip on duty. Frasier is an American comedy tv-series that was first aired in 1993 on NBC. See the best episodes of Frasier below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Miami Vice Best Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/miami-vice-best-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 09:01:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/miami-vice-best-episodes/</guid>
      <description>The story of the Miami Police Department&amp;rsquo;s vice squad and its efforts to end drug trafficking and prostitution, centered on the unlikely partnership of Sonny Crockett and Ricardo Tubbs - who first meet when Tubbs is undercover in a drug cartel. Miami Vice is an American drama, action &amp;amp; adventure tv-series that was first aired in 1984. See the best Miami Vice episodes below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Episodes of Scrubs</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-scrubs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 07:54:14 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-scrubs/</guid>
      <description>In the unreal world of Sacred Heart Hospital, John &amp;lsquo;J.D.&amp;rsquo; Dorian learns the ways of medicine, friendship and life. Scrubs is an American sitcom tv-series that was first aired in 2001. See the best Scrubs episodes below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Fear Factor Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-fear-factor-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 14:25:03 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-fear-factor-episodes/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Imagine a world where your greatest fears become reality.&amp;rdquo; In each pulse-racing &amp;ldquo;Fear Factor&amp;rdquo; episode, contestants recruited across the country battle in extreme stunts. These stunts are designed to challenge the contestants both physically and mentally. If a player is too afraid to complete or fail a stunt, the player is eliminated. If they succeed, they are one step closer to the grand prize: $50,000. See the best episodes of Fear Factor below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Episodes of Community</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-community/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 13:35:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-community/</guid>
      <description>Follow the lives of a group of students at what is possibly the world’s worst community college in the fictional locale of Greendale, Colorado. Community is an American comedy series that was first premiered in 2009. See the best Community episodes below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Episodes of Law and Order</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-law-and-order/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 10:08:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-law-and-order/</guid>
      <description>Follows a crime (usually a murder), usually adapted from current headlines, from two separate vantage points, the police investigation and the prosecution in court. Law and Order is an American police and legal drama tv series that was first premiered in 1990. See the best Law and Order episodes below to binge-watch on.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
