<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>comedy-central on </title>
    <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/network/comedy-central/</link>
    <description>Recent content in comedy-central on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 20:32:27 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bestepisodes.xyz/network/comedy-central/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Best Roast Comedy Central</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-roast-comedy-central/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 20:32:27 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-roast-comedy-central/</guid>
      <description>Putting a celebrity in the cross hairs of comedic barbs is what&amp;rsquo;s fun about this programme. A panel is selected, made up of the celebrity&amp;rsquo;s peers as well as popular comedians, who comically trash the `honoured guest&#39; both personally and professionally. Previously roasted celebrities include William Shatner, Flavor Flav, Pamela Anderson, David Hasselhoff and Denis Leary. Comedy Central Roasts is an American comedy roast tv-programme that was first aired in 2003. See the best Comedy Central Roasts episodes below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Episodes of Reno 911!</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-reno-911/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 16:37:57 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-reno-911/</guid>
      <description>This partially unscripted comedy brings viewers into the squad car as incompetent officers swing into action, answering 911 calls about everything from speeding violations and prostitution to staking out a drug den. Within each episode, viewers catch a &amp;lsquo;fly on the wall&amp;rsquo; glimpse of the cops&#39; often politically incorrect opinions, ranging from their personal feelings to professional critiques of their colleagues. See the best Reno 911 episodes below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Workaholics Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-workaholics-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 11:24:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-workaholics-episodes/</guid>
      <description>The misadventures of three recent college dropouts, roommates, and co-workers at a telemarketing company and their drug dealer. See the best episodes of Workaholics tv-show below.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
