<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>comedy-central on </title>
    <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/network/comedy-central/</link>
    <description>Recent content in comedy-central on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 10:46:14 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bestepisodes.xyz/network/comedy-central/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Best Episodes of Drunk History</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-drunk-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 10:46:14 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-drunk-history/</guid>
      <description>Historical reenactments from A-list talent as told by inebriated storytellers. A unique take on the familiar and less familiar people and events from America’s great past as great moments in history are retold with unforgettable results. Drunk History is an American educational comedy tv-series that was first aired in 2013. See the best Drunk History episodes below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Nathan for You Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-nathan-for-you-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 08:58:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-nathan-for-you-episodes/</guid>
      <description>Self-proclaimed business expert, writer, director and comedian Nathan Fielder helps real small businesses turn a profit with marketing tactics that no ordinary consultant would dare to attempt. From driving foot traffic to an off-the-strip souvenir shop by using Hollywood flair and a Johnny Depp impersonator, to creating a rebate that can only be redeemed by climbing a mountain, to founding a coffee shop called &amp;lsquo;Dumb Starbucks,&amp;rsquo; Nathan has always gone to the limit to make his ideas come to life. With his unorthodox approach to problem solving, Nathan’s genuine efforts to do good often draw the real people he encounters into an experience far beyond what they signed up for. Nathan For You is an American comedy documentary tv-series that was first aired in 2013 on comedy central. See the best episodes of Nathan For You below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Roast Comedy Central</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-roast-comedy-central/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 20:32:27 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-roast-comedy-central/</guid>
      <description>Putting a celebrity in the cross hairs of comedic barbs is what&amp;rsquo;s fun about this programme. A panel is selected, made up of the celebrity&amp;rsquo;s peers as well as popular comedians, who comically trash the `honoured guest&#39; both personally and professionally. Previously roasted celebrities include William Shatner, Flavor Flav, Pamela Anderson, David Hasselhoff and Denis Leary. Comedy Central Roasts is an American comedy roast tv-programme that was first aired in 2003. See the best Comedy Central Roasts episodes below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Episodes of Reno 911!</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-reno-911/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 16:37:57 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-reno-911/</guid>
      <description>This partially unscripted comedy brings viewers into the squad car as incompetent officers swing into action, answering 911 calls about everything from speeding violations and prostitution to staking out a drug den. Within each episode, viewers catch a &amp;lsquo;fly on the wall&amp;rsquo; glimpse of the cops&#39; often politically incorrect opinions, ranging from their personal feelings to professional critiques of their colleagues. See the best Reno 911 episodes below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Workaholics Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-workaholics-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 11:24:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-workaholics-episodes/</guid>
      <description>The misadventures of three recent college dropouts, roommates, and co-workers at a telemarketing company and their drug dealer. See the best episodes of Workaholics tv-show below.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
