<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>game-show on </title>
    <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/genres/game-show/</link>
    <description>Recent content in game-show on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 10:03:19 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bestepisodes.xyz/genres/game-show/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Best Hell&#39;s Kitchen Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-hells-kitchen-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 10:03:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-hells-kitchen-episodes/</guid>
      <description>Aspiring restaurateurs brave Ramsay and his fiery command of the kitchen as he puts the competitors through an intense culinary academy to prove they possess the right combination of ingredients to win a life-changing grand prize. Hell&amp;rsquo;s Kitchen is an American reality game-show tv-series that was first aired in 2005. See the best episodes of Hell&amp;rsquo;s Kitchen below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Forged in Fire Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-forged-in-fire-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 10:23:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-forged-in-fire-episodes/</guid>
      <description>Competitors re-create weapons from historical periods ranging from Japanese katanas to medieval broadswords to ancient throwing blades. Each entry is judged on its artistry as well as its functionality and accuracy. Forged in Fire is an American reality game-show tv-series that was first aired in 2015. See the best episodes of Forged in Fire below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Episodes of Chopped</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-chopped/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 16:49:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-episodes-of-chopped/</guid>
      <description>A high energy, fast paced cooking competition that challenges four up-and-coming chefs to turn a selection of everyday ingredients into an extraordinary three-course meal. After each course, a contestant gets “chopped” by our panel of esteemed culinary luminaries until the last man or woman left standing claims victory. See the best Chopped episodes below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Fear Factor Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-fear-factor-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 14:25:03 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/best-fear-factor-episodes/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Imagine a world where your greatest fears become reality.&amp;rdquo; In each pulse-racing &amp;ldquo;Fear Factor&amp;rdquo; episode, contestants recruited across the country battle in extreme stunts. These stunts are designed to challenge the contestants both physically and mentally. If a player is too afraid to complete or fail a stunt, the player is eliminated. If they succeed, they are one step closer to the grand prize: $50,000. See the best episodes of Fear Factor below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Running Man Funniest Episodes</title>
      <link>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/running-man-funniest-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 14:14:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestepisodes.xyz/tv-shows/running-man-funniest-episodes/</guid>
      <description>Running Man has one or more episodes streaming with subscription on Prime Video, and available for purchase on Prime Video. It has 297 episodes over 1 season. Running Man is still airing with no announced date for the next episode or season. See the best episodes of Running Man below.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
